Legends never die
when the world is calling you
Can you hear them screaming out your name?
Legends never die
they become a part of you
Every time you bleed for reaching greatness
Relentless you survive
They never lose hope when everything's cold and the fighting's near
It's deep in their bones they run into smoke when the fire is fierce
'Oh pick yourself up, cause
Legends never die
when the world is calling you
Can you hear them screaming out your name?
Legends never die
they become a part of you
Every time you bleed for reaching greatness
Legends never die
They're written down in eternity
But you'll never see the price it costs,
the scars collected all their lives
When everything’s lost
they pick up their hearts and avenge defeat
Before it all starts,
they suffer through harm
just to touch a dream
'Oh pick yourself up, cause
Legends never die
when the world is calling you
Can you hear them screaming out your name?
Legends never die
they become a part of you
Every time you bleed for reaching greatness
Legends never die